[{"answer": "Can I play", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yeah, I'm nice", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "One time that place scored fort", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I don't care", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "For what", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Taunting?", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "The coach from that place is going to be at the championship", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Chances are there's still a chance", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah?  So you up for a game later", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You don't wanna hurt your back", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Fuck you, my friend", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Who said I'm not getting recruited", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I mean it, give it your best shot, cause I'm tired of you holding that over my head", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I'm warning you.  You don't stall that bad attitude, no one's gonna recruit you", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Okay", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I've been hearing you", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Yeah, brothers are lined up at my locker", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Found?  I'm not some charity case", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Some girl that's been hanging on at every party.  now I'm supposed to be her baby's Daddy.  Anyway, I told your mom I wanted to be the one who told you", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I just told you", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Kiss my ass", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "my friend, please, last time you ches", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Who was that", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Who's nobody", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Who's nobody", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You want to go talk", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Oh, my friend, this is my friend.  my friend, my friend", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "We're going to get some food", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "How are you going to tell me what I have time for?  I mean, whatever I did...we can fix this", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "How are you going to tell me what I have time for?  I mean, whatever I did...we can fix this", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You don't think so", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Few days ago", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "my friend, my friend.  This ain't about us anymore, it's about me", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " How's he doing", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "What's that, not great", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " So, when do you go back", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "What do you mean", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Sometimes I wonder if it's worth it. Busting my ass, for what", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I don't know sometimes", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "So...how's the knee", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Strong enough to get you down the aisle", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Getting there", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yeah.  Two weeks.  I didn't get to send you an invitation, but if you..", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "What I'm trying to say is, I've loved you since I was eleven and the shit won't go away", "docId": "love_and_basketball.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I know, I probably should have said it two weeks ago", "qsentId": 46}]